My God . Please help me !
Oh , God !
( screams )
( banging )
Jason . It 's all done , Jason .
You 've done your job well , and Mommy is pleased .
That 's a good boy .
Now , come to Mommy . Come on .
Come on .
Mommy has a reward for you .
Jason , Mother is talking to you .
Come on .
That 's my boy . Come .
Kneel down .
That 's a boy .
Kneel down , Jason .
That 's my good boy .
That 's a good boy .
Good Jason .
( screams )
Ginny !
Come on . Let 's go . Ginny ?
Jesus !
Come on .
( thunder )
( dog howls )
( pole clatters )
Goddamn it , Harold ! I spent all day yesterday washing your clothes .
Look what you 're doing !
I work very hard trying to keep up with you
and all your sloppy habits . I get no help from you .
- ( TV ) The community of Crystal Lake - Jerk !
was shocked today with reports of a grisly mass murder .
Eight corpses have been discovered in what is being called
the most brutal and heinous crime in local history .
A police spokesman told " Eye On News "
that they 've been combing the area since before dawn
and are afraid that their gruesome discovery is just the beginning .
Police Chief Scott Fitzsimmons had no comment about the murders
when reached this morning . Detectives at the scene , however ,
were baffled by the brutality of the killings .
Bodies were found strewn over the four-square-mile camp ground
in the remote lake region .
Ginny Field miraculously survived repeated attacks
by the axe-wielding killer , and was taken to a local hospital today .
- My God ! - She is in a serious condition ,
- with multiple stab wounds . - ( clanging )
The names of the eight victims are being withheld
until notification of next of kin .
Reports of cannibalism are unconfirmed .
What are you doing out there ?
The person responsible for the horror remains at large .
( TV off )
Harold , I swear ...
Jesus Christ , Harold !
Just take what 's yours and leave the rest for me .
Very considerate .
You could 've at least finished the job .
Do I have to do everything around here ?
Harold ?
( creaking )
OK , boys , soup 's on .
What 's the matter , Lionel ? Aren 't you hungry ? It 's good .
Here . Here , look . I 'm eating .
Very good .
Dayfly eggs ?
Hey ! Hey , hey , hey !
C 'mon . If Edna catches you in here , she 'll make a fur coat of you .
C 'mon , I 'll take you home .
( burps )
Didn 't I feed you enough for supper ?
The doctor said you have to lose weight , didn 't he ?
I 'm trying to help you , but you keep sneaking food behind my back .
What am I gonna do with you ?
And put that filthy animal back where it belongs . Come on .
Hey , hey , hey ! What are you so nervous about ? Come on .
Who would do something like this ?
What 's the matter ? What happened ?
It 's all that crap you 've been stuffing yourself with !
( TV ) It 's " Easy Money " time , the show where everybody wins !
Where 's that other needle ?
( splattering )
( TV ) Thank you , Johnny , and good evening .
It 's " Easy Money " , Charlie Lincoln , and I 'm here to give away money .
I 've got a pocketful of money burning a hole in my pocket ...
Harold ?
( TV ) 14 straight weeks in a row .
( TV ) That 's not the end .
Harold ?
( rattling )
( screams )
( stifled scream )
( horn )
It 's the white house on the left .
- Shelly , come and meet your date . - Bring her to me !
Maybe this wasn 't such a good idea .
Sex , sex , sex . You guys are getting boring , you know that ?
What would a weekend in the country be without sex ?
- Cool it , Andy . - I didn 't mean it that way .
I want you to have a good time this weekend .
What happened to me at the lake happened a long time ago .
I 'm fine , OK ? Just forget about me .
Forget that we 've been friends ...
( yells )
Goddamn it , Shelly ! Why do you always have to be such an asshole ?
I beg your pardon . I 'm not an asshole . I 'm an actor .
Same thing .
Look , Shelly , you 're my roommate and I like you . Most of the time .
But you 've gotta quit doing those things .
Now , I got you a date , didn 't I ?
- Yeah . - So don 't embarrass me .
Just relax . Be yourself .
Would you be yourself , if you looked like this ?
( knocking )
- Yes ? - Hi , Mrs. Sanchez . I 'm Chris .
We 've come to pick up Vera .
She is not going !
( argument in Spanish )
- What are they saying ? - I don 't know . I flunked Spanish .
Hi , everybody . What are you looking at ?
Is everything alright ?
Just your basic old-fashioned mother problems .
So , which one 's my date ?
Hi .
You 're Shelly ?
Sorry .
Hey , the van 's on fire !
Is that all you two are gonna do this weekend ? Smoke dope ?
Why not , man ? Is there a law against it ?
There are better things to do .
- Like what ? - I can 't think of anything .
Hey , Chrissy ? How much further to the lake ?
We 'd be there if some people didn 't need the bathroom every five minutes .
That 's what happens when you 're pregnant .
Sure , why not ?
Let 's share the wealth with those less fortunate up front here !
Yeah !
What have you got in there ?
My whole world .
In that little thing ?
Stick around . You 'll see .
( sirens )
It 's the cops !
- Oh , my God ! - They 're catching us .
- What are we gonna do ? - Destroy the evidence ! Hurry !
- No way , man . - Let 's go , Chuck ! Come on !
- They 're gaining . - Throw it out !
- They 'll see it . - Get rid of it . Eat it .
- ( Shelly ) We 're going to jail ! - I 'm driving .
- Breakfast ? - No way ! We 're pregnant .
Faster ! Eat faster !
Why don 't you help us ?
Oh , I guess I 'm just not hungry .
You 're always hungry , Shelly . Come on , eat !
- I 'm allergic . - I gotta pull over .
- Oh , man ! - Oh , no !
Shit !
( radio ) 624 , Charlie 63 is unable to handle ...
Help the ambulance . I 'll get the crowd .
OK , guys , show 's over . Move it back over here , alright ?
Kiddo , don 't let your imagination run away with you .
( buzzing flies )
- Chris , stop the van ! Stop ! - What is it ?
- What are you doing ? - You almost ran over him !
I was daydreaming . I didn 't see him .
Hey , he looks just like my grandfather !
Why ,
I must be in heaven !
Don 't touch him . You don 't know where he 's been .
- Thank you . Thank you . - Sleeping in the road ?
You are , indeed , all of you , kind and generous young people .
Look upon what His grace has brought unto me !
- What is that ? - I found this today .
- There were other parts of the body . - That 's an eyeball !
And He said that He wanted me to have this . This !
He wanted me to warn you ! Look upon this omen
and go back from whence ye came !
I have warned thee !
I ... have warned thee .
Check it out ! Whoo-hoo !
Why don 't we take our bags into the house first ?
Chris , come on down .
You go ahead . I 'll take my bags in the house and look around .
Hello ?
Is someone here ?
( screams )
Rick !
Is it my imagination or did it just get cold in here ?
Did I do something wrong ? Did I ?
No . It 's just being here again .
I know it 's only two years but I feel like I 've been away for ever .
Doesn 't look like anything 's changed , though .
Even the paintings are still crooked .
Well , you 've certainly changed . Don 't you even say hello any more ?
I 'm sorry .
- Hello , Rick . How are you ? - Well , that 's a start .
Could you slow down , please ?
There 's a whole weekend ahead . Let me get to know you again .
Get to know this place again .
OK . But there 's only so many cold showers I can take .
Come outside and help me with the bags .
Oh , God !
You know , Chris , I think you 've gained weight since last summer .
I have not !
You creep ! Put me down .
You get the ones inside , I 'll get the ones off the top .
Wasn 't this door closed a few minutes ago ?
- What did you say ? - Nothing .
Chris ...
- ( screams ) - That 's my bag . I 'll take it .
Shelly , why aren 't you at the lake with everybody else ?
Oh , they said they were going skinny-dipping .
I 'm not skinny enough .
This was my bedroom . It 's yours for the weekend .
Great .
Chris ? I don 't mean to be picky or anything , but where 's the bed ?
Chris ?
Oh !
It 's right here .
- What 's this ? - It 's your bed .
- A hammock ? - You might like it .
Why not ?
Where 's the bed ?
Alright .
Chris , I don 't understand ... why you guys have so much hay .
You don 't have any horses . Never did .
It 's my father 's idea . Every year , he plans to buy a horse .
Every year , he buys all this hay but no horse . You figure it out .
You realize , of course ... that I gave up an opportunity
to spend the weekend with Mary Jo Conrad for this .
You actually gave up the chance
to be with the Mary Jo Conrad for little old me ?
That 's right .
Boy , are you dumb !
Chris , I realize I 'm just a dumb country boy
and my feelings don 't matter .
But this is the sweat of a worker on my forehead , not of a lover .
Now , I believe
that there is a time and a place for everything .
And now 's the time , and now 's the place , if you know what I mean .
So what I think we should do
is set aside three hours a day to fulfill our needs .
One in the morning ... and two at night .
If you agree , I agree .
Were you talking to me ?
( scream )
- Is anyone in here ? - What 's going on ?
You check down here . I 'll check the upstairs .
( creaking )
Is anybody in there ?
( thud )
( screams )
Don 't look at him . Let 's get out of here .
- We heard screaming . - Oh , my God !
What happened to him ?
- Don 't touch him , Andy ! - Don 't move him !
You creep ! Get up !
I guess I fooled you , huh ?
- You jerk ! - Chris , he doesn 't know any better .
It was a joke !
- Chris . - It was just a joke !
- I didn 't mean to ... - You never mean to .
I gotta get outta here . I 'm going to the store .
- Can I use your car ? - Sure .
Thanks .
Asshole !
Hey ! Hey , hey , hey ! Let me go with you !
I gotta get out of here , too !
( horn )
Chris . Chris , wait up .
What 's wrong ?
It 's that creep Shelly . What a sick sense of humor .
That 's just his way of getting attention .
He doesn 't know what happened .
I know it , Deb .
But from the minute we got here , I 've been seeing and hearing things .
It 's probably just my imagination .
I shouldn 't have come back here so soon .
Don 't let it get to you . Relax . Enjoy the weekend .
Nothing 's going to happen when we 're all here together .
OK .
Hey , how are things with Rick going ?
But he just doesn 't understand .
That 'll be $ 18.50 .
We don 't accept no food stamps .
Shelly !
I need some money .
Excuse me , but I believe that 's my wallet .
Make a wish .
Can I buy you guys a beer or something ?
I 'll take that now .
Is this your rubber ?
Didn 't your momma teach you manners ?
If you want something , you ask .
- Nice ! - Please , be cool !
May I please have the wallet ?
You mean , " May I please have the wallet , ma 'am ? "
May I please have the wallet , ma 'am ?
That 's good . That 's real nice .
Hey , that was a 20 !
- Are they following us ? - No !
- Good ! - Here . You drive .
The way I feel , I 'd probably get us into an accident .
Next time , I 'll know how to handle a situation like that .
Let 's just hope next time isn 't too soon .
Uh-oh .
( engine starts )
Oh , shit !
" Oh , shit ! " is right . Let 's get outta here .
Hold on !
- What 're you doing ? ! - He went too far this time !
Oh , shit !
- I did it . Did I do it ? - Yes , you did it .
- You were great . - I was great .
You son of a bitch ! You ought to come back here , you bastard !
You ain 't getting away with this ! I 'm gonna get you !
- Let 's go get some exercise . - This is all the exercise I need .
That was close .
You better watch out with that thing .
Come on . I 'm warning you , Andy . I 'll break your string !
What happened to them ?
What happened to your windshield , man ?
We had a slight misunderstanding with a motorcycle gang .
But Shelly made ' em see the error of their ways .
It was nothing .
My poor car ! What did you do to it ?
Erm ... Yeah , we 're real sorry , you know ? But it wasn 't our fault .
A few minor repairs , it 'll be good as new .
That 's it . I 've had it .
It seemed a good idea to spend some time together ,
but this is more than I bargained for .
Where are you going ?
Away from here .
Stay with me .
- Why should I ? - Because I want you to .
You don 't play fair , do you ? Get in .
( door creaks )
- Let 's go for a swim . - I don 't know .
Come on . We 'll be all alone . We can do whatever we want .
- Nobody 'll see . - Sounds disgusting ! Let 's go .
I 'll grab a couple of towels . See you down there .
( barks )
- Maybe we shouldn 't do this , Ali . - We gotta even the score .
Nobody 's gonna get hurt , baby .
- Right ! - Trust me .
- Let me do it . - I know what I 'm doing .
( clanking )
( rustling )
Oh , shit ...
Who 's up there ?
Here , take this in the barn and start pouring . And find Fox .
( Fox ) Whooo !
What the hell are you doing ?
Get off that thing !
Whoo !
This feels good !
Ali is gonna be pissed he sees you screwing around !
Now , come on . We got shit to do .
What the hell ?
Fox ?
Where are you ?
Stop screwing around .
You 're messing everything up !
You 're dead now , woman .
Fox !
Fox ! Loco !
Open the damn door !
Fox !
What the hell are you guys doing up there ? You hear me talking to you ?
When I find you , you bastard , you 're a dead man !
Shit !
I don 't wanna go home . This is fun .
- What are you doing ? - We haven 't been in the barn ...
We haven 't been in the barn . Let 's take a look .
Not now . I 'm cold .
C 'mon , how about a roll in the hay ?
Go play with yourself . I 'm going into the house .
Hey , wait up !
- That better ? - Yeah . Thanks .
You know , I don 't think I could live anywhere else .
The nights are so peaceful and quiet here .
- It 's deceiving . - What do you mean ?
The quiet can fool you . It fooled me .
Chris , why 'd you come back here ?
To prove something to myself .
To prove I 'm stronger than I think I am .
What about us ?
I 'm here with you . Isn 't that enough ?
I don 't know ! I don 't see you for months on end .
When I do , you put this barrier up between us . How do I break through ?
- You give up ? - You out of your mind ?
- Do you give up ? - Ha-ha ! Never !
I know how to stop this .
Andy ? I can think of much better things you can do with your hands .
You win !
I guess that leaves you and me . Sort of .
Yep .
You really are very good at that .
It 's nothing .
Vera , you and I have gotten to know each other a little today .
I like you .
I like you a lot . I was thinking that maybe , y 'know , we could ...
I don 't think so . I 'm going outside for a few minutes .
When I get back in , we 'll talk . OK ?
Sure . We 'll talk .
Bitch .
( footfalls )
( creaking )
- How do we do it ? - First , we take our clothes off .
Then you get on top of me , or I could get on top of you .
I know how to do it . How do we do it in a hammock ?
Well ... I think you can figure something out .
I 'll think of something .
You 're right . I should have told you a long time ago but I couldn 't .
You don 't have to if you don 't want to .
I want to . I want you to know what happened so you 'll understand .
Everything is so clear in my mind , as if it were happening right now .
I don 't know if you remember ,
but when you dropped me off that night , it was very late .
I knew my parents would be waiting , but I didn 't care .
We had such a good time .
The minute I walked in , my parents started yelling at me and cursing me .
We had such a big fight .
My mom slapped me .
That was the first time my mother hit me . I couldn 't believe it .
I ran out the door and into the woods .
I wanted to punish them . So I decided to hide out all night .
I thought I 'd get them so worried , they 'd be sorry for what they did .
It had been raining . The woods were cold and wet .
But I found a dry spot under an old oak tree .
I guess I fell asleep .
All I can remember next
is being startled out of sleep by the sound of footsteps .
I was sure it was Dad , so I sat up and listened for him .
But the footsteps stopped .
Then there was this cracking noise behind me .
I turned around
and standing there was this hideous-looking man !
( screams )
He was so grotesque , he was almost inhuman !
He had a knife !
And he attacked me with it !
I was so hysterical , I don 't know how I was even able to think ,
but I kicked the knife out of his hands and I ran !
He ran after me . He caught me and pulled me to the ground .
I was kicking and screaming and yelling , but it didn 't do any good !
He dragged me along the ground .
I blacked out .
I don 't know what happened after that , I just don 't know !
Chris ? It 's alright . You 're alright .
When I woke up , I was in my own bed .
My parents have never said a word about it .
They act as if the whole thing never happened , but it did .
All I want is to just forget it , but I can 't !
I 'll never forget that horrible face ! Never !
What 's that ?
Damn it , it 's that battery .
I charged it yesterday . It must not have taken .
It may just start anyway . Let me try .
( engine won 't start )
We 're gonna have to walk back . It 's OK .
- OK ? - Yeah .
I know a pretty good short cut .
( rustling )
Shelly ?
( banging )
Heavy shit !
Who 's there ?
Shelly , if this is another of your tricks ...
Sorry ! I didn 't mean to scare you .
Between you and Shelly , I 'm lucky I haven 't had a heart attack !
What 's Butterball up to now ?
I don 't know . He just ducked into the barn .
Let 's give him some of his own medicine .
I don 't think he 's in here . Let 's go back .
( Chuck ) Hey .
Maybe that wasn 't him .
- Chili . - Shh !
Yaaa !
I guess he must 've left .
Come on , let 's get out of here !
I 'm not going to let anybody hurt you .
Gee , thanks . I feel a lot better now .
( screams )
( yells )
That 'll teach you a valuable lesson .
A beautiful girl like you should never go out in the dark alone .
Damn it , Shelly !
Why do you do these stupid things ?
- I have to . - No . You don 't have to .
- I just want you to like me . - I do like you .
But not when you act like a jerk .
Being a jerk is better than being a nothing .
I never said you were nothing .
You don 't have to say it . I could tell .
You 're wrong ! Shelly !
( rustling )
Chuck ? Chili ?
Hey ! What 're you guys doing in there ?
Are you guys doing something I shouldn 't see ?
( yells )
( owl hoots )
( twig snaps )
Oh , that 's great !
Hey , I dropped your wallet .
I 'm sorry . I got it .
Who are you ?
What 're you doing ?
Cut that out right now . That 's not funny .
That was the best one yet .
Was it you , me or the hammock ?
- I vote for me . - Hmm ? I vote for the hammock .
Where you going ?
Taking a shower . You ought to try it sometime .
- Hey , Debbie . Can you hear me ? - Barely .
( Andy ) I 'm gonna go downstairs and get a brew . You want one ?
- ( door creaks ) - Andy ?
Oh , Jesus !
- Do you want a beer or not ? - Sure .
- Alright . Be right back . - OK .
Andy ?
- Andy ! - Yeah ?
Are you still out there ?
( screams )
( Debbie ) I can 't hear you .
Andy ?
Would you quit fooling around ?
Cut it out .
Andy ? I changed my mind . I don 't want that beer .
Andy ?
Did you hear me about that beer ?
Andy !
Oh , God , I hate when you don 't answer me .
What ?
Where 's this coming from ?
Great short cut , Rick .
- Come on ! Let 's move it . - Always spoiling my fun .
- ( rustling ) - What was that noise ?
- What ? - I heard something over there .
Come on , let 's get home .
( rattling and popping )
- Did I hear you screaming ? - No .
It 's probably Debbie having an orgasm .
How come you never scream when we have sex ?
Give me something to scream about .
- ( screams ) - What 's the matter ?
Nothing . I was just practicing .
Don 't do that to me !
Here . Go down the cellar and check the fuse box .
In the dark ? Alone ?
Be a man , man .
Nothing to be afraid of , man . So what if it 's dark ?
Nothing to be afraid of .
( squelching )
Oh ! Jeez !
Oh , God !
Hmm !
( chuckles ) Alright .
( rattling )
Who 's there ?
( thud )
Chuck ? You back already ?
Well , at least you got the outside lights working .
Nice make-up job .
( groans )
Stop fooling around , man .
That 's better .
( cries out )
( electricity fizzles )
What 's going on ?
Get up !
Shelly ! Enough is enough !
Oh , my God !
( screams )
Andy ? Debbie ?
Shelly 's dead !
He 's dead !
Andy ! Deb ?
No !
Oh , my God ! Oh , my God !
( wind howls )
( screams )
This wind sure came up .
Seems awfully quiet .
Hard to believe the Wild Bunch is already in bed .
Who knows , with those guys ?
I can 't get this door open . There 's something behind it .
- I smell something burning . - Take this . Let me do it .
No wonder . Some idiot put this chair there . Something is burning .
Lights aren 't working , either .
Real smart ! What 's going on here ?
You tell me . They 're your friends .
I 'll go to the living room and check what 's going on there .
Andy ? Debbie ? You guys up there ?
Anybody here ?
- Everybody 's taken off . - They wouldn 't do that .
I don 't know what 's going on . I 'll go out and take a look around .
Rick , wait , I wanna come with you .
( twig snaps )
Andy ? Is that you ?
Rick ?
Rick !
Is everything alright ?
( crunching )
( dripping )
( gasps ) Eew !
Where 's that coming from ?
I don 't know what game you guys are playing , but I don 't like it .
Debbie ? You guys up here ?
Hey , come on , you guys . You 're wrecking the house .
Rick !
( wind howls )
( screams )
Rick ! Where are you ?
( banging )
( wind blows door open )
Rick ! Help me !
( screams )
Rick !
Rick ! Rick !
( screams )
( lock clicks )
( whimpers )
( screams )
( groans )
No !
Keys . Keys !
Come on !
( engine starts )
( engine splutters )
What 's happening ?
No !
( engine won 't start )
Come on ! Come on !
Gas !
( engine starts )
( screams )
( doors rattle )
You can 't be alive .
You !
( screams )
Motherfucking psycho !
( repeated blows )
No !
( frogs croak )
( bird calls )
( screams )
( flapping and screaming )
No !
No , no , no ...
( screams )
Looks like she 's the only one alive .
What was that about a lady in the lake ?
She must 've flipped out . Poor kid 's been through hell .
I 'll take her .
( gasps and whimpers )
( screaming )
It 's OK . You 're gonna be alright . You 're gonna be fine .